(Raj:)So she's gonna be laid up
for at least six weeks.
(Leonard:)Poor Mrs. Wolowitz.
(Amy:)Should we do something for her?
(Sheldon:)I know. Let's go see
the new Spider-Man movie.
(Amy:)Sheldon, we're talking about
your friend's mother. She got hurt.
(Sheldon:)I thought that subject had run
its course, so I changed it.
(Sheldon:)It's called reading the room, Amy.
(Howard:)-Hi.
-Hey, how were things on the set?
(Penny:)Pretty good, actually.
(Raj:)So the movie's
not as bad as you thought?
(Penny:)Oh, no, it is, but I decided,
instead of complaining about it,
(Penny:)I'm just gonna go in
every day and give it my all.
(Amy:)-Good for you.
-Thanks.
(Penny:)There's no reason
why I shouldn't be the best
(Penny:)bisexual go-go dancer
slowly transforming
(Penny:)into a killer gorilla
anyone's ever seen.
(Leonard:)I don't know. The bisexual gorilla
go-go dancer in Schindler's List
(Leonard:)is tough to beat.
(Sheldon:)Ah, very good.
(Sheldon:)Because a gorilla go-go dancer
of any sexual preference
(Sheldon:)would be out of place in a film
about the Holocaust.